Who are these...
shadowy soldiers?!
Where'd they come from?
I-Impossible...
How?
What is he doing here?
Mr. Song, this means the broadcast
was shut down, right?
What in the world is happening over there?
It's no good. There's too much
confusion at the scene.
We need to confirm the status of our hunters.
Gather all the intel we can.
Yes, sir.
Director!
Calls are coming in so fast that
the phone system is crashing!
They're demanding we resume the broadcast!
We would if we could!
But we're not getting any word from
the scene, much less any footage!
Besides... What do we do
if all the S-Ranks are dead?!
Hey, answer me!
What is going on over there?!
Damn it! Camera's not working...
Now, of all times!
Iron!
Go.
I'm not following any of this.
Just who are those shadows?
And how is Hunter Sung even here?
Hunter Sung! When did you get to the island?
And how?
I can explain later.
First, let's treat your wounds.
Drink this.
Wait, I can't transfer these...
Some sort of medicine? From summoning magic?
Mr. Ma.
Please open your mouth.
What the...
My wounds... They're healed.
She's not recovering.
Why isn't it working?
It's just like before.
Not good. Her aura is getting
weaker and weaker.
She's too badly hurt for me to heal.
We need to get out of here, fast.
I'll clear a path.
Got it.
Hold on!
They swarm just like bugs, too.
There's just too many!
Chairman!
What condition is the strike team in?
We're still unsure.
Something has temporarily interrupted
all comms from the island.
We've been trying to contact Japanese
command, but we can't get through.
The civilian media hasn't seen anything
since the black ant appeared, either.
We need to restore signal as soon as possible!
Make sure the medic and retrieval teams
are ready to move ASAP!
Yes, sir!
I have never...
resented my aging body and heart
as much as I do right now.
Even if I couldn't help,
I wish I could fight at their sides.
Chairman...
Please, let them be all right.
Ugh! What is this?!
First the feed cuts, and now
the TV breaks?! Unbelievable!
I don't think that's helping, honey.
I'm gonna watch in my room.
Maybe I can find some updates on my phone.
Such a restless girl.
What is happening? Explain.
Goto's vital signs are silent.
From what we can tell
before the signal was cut,
there was a powerful enemy that appeared.
It's likely he was killed.
And the others?
We're in the process of verifying.
Well, make it fast!
Any further losses will cost us
in the next phase.
Yes, sir.
Goto got himself killed? The useless oaf!
What in the hell is happening on that island?
Elites like Igris and Iron
are doing well enough,
but the foot soldiers are
at a bit of a disadvantage.
Part of me wants to boost their numbers,
but with this many people watching?
No.
Everyone.
This isn't getting us anywhere.
I'm going to get a bit more aggressive
about clearing our path.
The rest of you...
Please stay behind him.
The other shadows will fight off the ants.
Should any get past, please deal with them.
Understood. We can still handle that much.
Yeah!
And I also need to ask you: please keep
what you're about to see to yourselves.
Is he...?
He's back.
Does that mean...
that Goto lost?!
There was no king outside.
Is he in here?
The one you would call king?
He's the reason I can't sense
the shadow I sent with Goto.
Wha—
H-Hey!
Is it you?
Are you the king of humans?
Huh...
Fancy that. A talking bug.
Human.
What a powerful aura.
But you're still just a bug.
Even for Hunter Sung...
This might be too much!
Director! We've got the feed back!
Wha?!
What the...
Resume the broadcast! Do it now!
But if we do that, we'll be
broadcasting live with no delay!
If something happens, we won't
be able to stop it getting out!
We already cut the broadcast once.
I don't see how it can get worse!
Do it!
R-Right!
Our fate—no, the outcome of this battle—
depends on this man!
M-Mr. Song!
I can't believe it...
Isn't that...
No way! How?!
Jinwoo?!
He said he was just stepping out!
Again with this?!
Hunter Sung made it!
But how did he get to the island?
I wouldn't worry about that!
Let's put our faith in him.
If he's a mage type,
why would he get so close?!
He underestimated the ant...
and got nailed for it!
Weak.
You must not be the king after all.
Master Baek. Master Choi.
Is he really a mage?
I have no idea anymore.
I certainly wasn't expecting this.
He's pretty durable. Is it the exoskeleton?
What a fearsome battle.
I'm an A-Rank, and it's all
I can do to stay on my feet.
The flow of magic power is enough
to almost make me pass out.
I'm being... forced back?
How?
What in the world...
is this human?!
What is this?
A mixture of toxins from
marine life in this area,
with my magic power amplifying its potency.
You should no longer even be able to move.
This is the end for you.
Die, human!
Seven KIA in a ten-man team?
Is this some kind of joke?
No, sir, it's the facts.
We were able to contact
the surviving hunters to confirm.
We lost over half our hunters?!
This is a fiasco!
We've also detected a powerful reading
near the island's caldera.
It's likely the magic beast that defeated Goto.
How is it still alive after fighting him?!
And it's headed into the nest? Why?
There's no telling.
It could have some objective,
or maybe it was injured enough
to want to return home.
We weren't able to confirm
the survival of the Korean hunters.
If they're still alive, they're going to run
into that thing that was able to kill Goto.
There's no way they can win
when they're already exhausted.
The ants will be weak
from all the fighting, as well.
If we can strike down the strong one,
the others will just be fodder.
We can still come out of this on top.
Hurry and recover the survivors!
As soon as they've joined the second strike
team at sea, send them back to the island!
And that about covers it. A chopper
will be there to pick you up shortly.
Copy that.
We're moving to plan 9. Let's go.
It's hopeless.
That thing... is a monster.
We don't... stand a chance.
Get a grip! We don't have time
for panic attacks!
No one can beat that thing!
We need to run! If we don't, we'll die!
Pathetic.
And we don't have a choice, anyway.
Wasn't he poisoned? Is he all right?
At this point, nothing can surprise me anymore.
So you had a secret weapon.
No wonder you seemed
to be taking it easy earlier.
Maybe it's because my perception ability
has gotten so high...
but I can sense his feelings—
his anxiety.
Well, that makes two of us.
I need to end this as soon as I can!
Poison is ineffective.
Tests of strength are pointless.
In that case...
Speed comparable to my own.
And yet, he grows even faster.
How is this possible?
Upgrade... Mutilation.
Wha... What is this?!
How?!
Regeneration, huh?
What is this?
What in the world was that?!
Just who... is this human?
This human!
Go.
How is this possible?
I was born to be the strongest.
I devour all, growing ever more powerful...
I should be king. And yet now...
Run...
I must run!
I must run to survive!
To get as far away as possible!
Hurry! Hurry!
I must hurry and get away!
The ants...
They're fleeing?
Did we win?
Hunter Sung!
Her aura is fading...
We're almost out of time.
Let's get out of here, fast!
A recovery helicopter
should be waiting outside!
If we can get on board—
No. I'm not sure she'll last that long.
Then what do we—
I thought potions didn't work.
I haven't tried this one.
The Elixir of Life that cured
Mom's Eternal Sleep...
This is our last hope.
It's ineffective?
Did it not work?
Leaving the island normally won't be
fast enough. Potions aren't working.
And I need more time before
I can use Shadow Exchange again!
Is there... nothing else I can do?